Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 35mm Microfilm Proofs, 1906-1960 and undated RL.00657
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Domestic Advertisements, 1906-1941; 1
  - Sonora Phonograph Co. (phonograph, radio speakers), 1924-1926 (Film-reel 35)
  - Stork Co. (baby pants, sheeting), 1914-1916 (Film-reel 35)
  - S.W. Straus & Co. (banking), 1925-1932 (Film-reel 35)
  - Sun Maid Raisin Growers, 1923-1925 (Film-reel 35)
  - Sun Maid Raisin Growers, 1925-1929 (Film-reel 36)
  - Superior Underwear Co., 1914-1919 (Film-reel 36)
  - Stewart Phonograph Co., 1921 (Film-reel 36)
  - Union Tobacco Co. (Herbert Taryton cigarettes), 1928-1929 (Film-reel 36)
  - Tea Garden Products Co. (preserves, jellies), 1934-1935 (Film-reel 36)
  - Tested Products Laboratories Inc. (Placidon stomach relief), 1934 (Film-reel 36)
  - Tex-a-kan Flour Mills Co., 1936-1937 (Film-reel 36)
  - Tydol (gasoline), 1917-1919 (Film-reel 36)
  - Time, Fortune (magazines), 1929-1933 (Film-reel 36)
  - Toledo Scale Co., 1929 (Film-reel 36)
  - Thermoid Rubber Co. (Hardy universal joints, industrial machinery accessories, tires), 1919-1921 (Film-reel 36)
  - Thermoid Rubber Co. (Hardy universal joints, industrial machinery accessories, tires), 1916-1923 (Film-reel 37)
  - Town House Hotel, 1936-1937 (Film-reel 37)
  - Tromite Corporation (water softener), 1923-1924 (Film-reel 37)
  - Trussed Concrete Steel Co. (building materials), 1914-1917 (Film-reel 37)
  - International Telephone & Telegraph (postal telegraph, commercial cables), 1929-1931 (Film-reel 37)
  - United Airlines (Air Express Division, passenger flights), 1933-1937 (Film-reel 37)
  - United Airlines (Air Express Division, passenger flights), 1937-1939 (Film-reel 38)
  - United Artists (Hal Roach Studios, Captain Fury), 1939 (Film-reel 38)
  - United States Rubber Co. (rubber footwear, Raynsters raincoats, Keds sneakers, Naugahyde traveling bags), 1919-1928 (Film-reel 38)
  - U.S. Industrial Alcohol Co. (Pyro antifreeze, Alcorub rubbing alcohol), 1925-1933 (Film-reel 39)
  - Urbana Wine Co. (Gold Seal champagne and wines), 1934 (Film-reel 39)
  - Vauv Co. (publications), 1924-1927 (Film-reel 39)
  - Vogue (publication), 1914 (Film-reel 39)
  - P.F. Volland Co. (publishers), 1914 (Film-reel 39)
  - S. Sternau (sterno canned heat, Erno nose spray, Spry rubbing compound), 1929-1938 (Film-reel 39)
  - Davison Chemical Corp. (Sylox baby powder), 1939 (Film-reel 39)
  - Wadsworth Watch Case Co., 1921-1929 (Film-reel 39)
  - Wadsworth Watch Case (Henrietta cases), 1937-1938 (Film-reel 39)
  - John Wanamaker (department store), 1914 (Film-reel 39)
  - Washington State Progress Commission (promotion), 1938 (Film-reel 39)
  - W.R. Warner Co. (Sloan's linament, Formamint, Agarol, Stacomb), 1923- (Film-reel 39)
  - Mrs. EmilyWatson, Inc. (pie crust), 1924-1927 (Film-reel 39)
  - Welch Grape Juice Co. (Grapelade), 1925-1928 (Film-reel 39)
  - Welch Grape Juice Co. (Grapelade), 1925-1928 (Film-reel 40)
  - Wheeler-Osgood Co. (Laminex doors), 1929-1931 (Film-reel 40)
  - Charles William Co. (stores), 1914 (Film-reel 40)
  - Wood Associates (office furniture), 1930 (Film-reel 40)
  - Wm. Wrigley (chewing gum), 1931-1934 (Film-reel 40)
- Foreign Proofs Previous to 1934, undated; 2
  - Alexandra (Egypt), undated; 1
    - Quaker Oats, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Shelltox, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Peak Prean, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Jantzen, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Victor, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Gillette, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Dollar Line, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet trucks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet passenger cars, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Buick, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Institutional, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors, undated (Film-reel 41)
  - Antwerp (Belgium), undated; 2
    - General Motors, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Pontiac, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Buick--Marquette, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Utility truck, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Complete line, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Victor, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Zoo candies, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - De Kuyper's liqueurs, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Eastman Kodak, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Fyffe's bananas, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Felix cat food, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Flexo watch crystals, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Frigidaire, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Gillette, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Carpal, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - CeCe radio tubes, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Chile saltpetre, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Coca-Cola, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Goodrich, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Victor, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Jantzen, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Johnson Sea Horses, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Kraft, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Extrait de Viande Liebig, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Cutex, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - De Beukelaer, undated (Film-reel 41)
  - Batavia (Java), undated; 3
    - General Motors, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Buick, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Cadillac, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Johnson Sea Horses, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Eastman Kodak, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Goodrich, undated (Film-reel 41)
  - Berlin (Germany), undated; 4
    - Johnson Sea Horses, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet trucks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet passenger cars, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Marquette, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Oakland, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Oldsmobile, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Pontiac, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Vauxhall, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Acrophon, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Bakelite, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Chile saltpetre, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Coca-Cola, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Eastman Kodak, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Electrola, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Gillette, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Goodrich, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Victor, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Alpine--Gruen watches, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Horlicks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Jantzen, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Kraft, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Pond's, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Quaker Oats, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Blondex, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Royal baking powder, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Sun Maid raisins, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Sagrotan, undated (Film-reel 41)
  - Bombay (Mumbai, India), undated; 5
    - General Motors, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Buick, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet trucks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet passenger cars, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Vauxhall, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Pontiac, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Opel, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--GMC, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Wotto Brady & Co. Ltd, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Eastman Kodak, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Edsu fabrics, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Goodrich, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Horlicks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Johnson & Johnson, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Royal baking powder, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Scott's Emulsion, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Silk Flakes, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Tata Oil Mills Co., Ltd., undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Tata Oil Mills Co., Ltd.--501 soap, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Tata Oil Mills Co., Ltd.--Cocogem, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Tata Oil Mills Co., Ltd.--Tej boot polish, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Tata Oil Mills Co., Ltd.--Challak motor polish, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Mobil Oil, undated (Film-reel 41)
  - Bucharest (Romania/Rumania), undated; 6
    - General Motors, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Opel, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Eastman Kodak, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Gilbert & Parker, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Goodyear, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Columbia Records, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Pond's, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Ivanhoe Perfection stove, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Sare de Lux, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Standard Oil, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Prestone, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Electrogay, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Telephone Co., undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Chat Noir & Lady cosmetics, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Carn cigarettes, undated (Film-reel 41)
  - Buenos Aires (Argentina), undated; 7
    - General Motors, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet trucks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Oakland, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Pontiac, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Buick, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Cadillac, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Oldsmobile, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet passenger cars, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Brasso, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Dunlap, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Eastman Kodak, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Frigidaire, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Electric, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Goodrich, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Modess, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Karpal, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - National City Bank, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Nael candies, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Overseas Motor Service Corp., undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Overseas Motor Service Corp.--New Departure, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Overseas Motor Service Corp.--Hycoe, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Overseas Motor Service Corp.--Delco-Remy, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Padilla vermouth, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Pond's, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Pyrrhocide, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Royal baking powder, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Santos cigars, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Sonora, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Waldorf tissues, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Swift's, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Por Taytoy milk, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - J. Walter Thompson, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Standard Oil, undated (Film-reel 41)
  - Montreal and Toronto (Canada), undated; 8
    - Gruen, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Goodrich, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Gillette, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Fleischmann's baking powder, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Fleischmann's yeast for health, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Royal yeast cakes, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Shell Oil, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - J. Walter Thompson, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Kraft, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Magic baking powder, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Libby's, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Lafayette, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Windsor Duo towel, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Chase & Sanborn coffee, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Clover Leaf salmon, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Cream of Wheat, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Cutex, undated (Film-reel 41)
  - Copenhagen (Denmark), undated; 9
    - General Motors, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--GMC, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Imi, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Jantzen, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Jonarista, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Odo-ro-no, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Ota, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Overseas Motor Service Corp., undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Overseas Motor Service Corp.--AC spark plugs, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Overseas Motor Service Corp.--Delco-Remy, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Overseas Motor Service Corp.--Lonejoy, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Overseas Motor Service Corp.--New Departure, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Overseas Motor Service Corp.--Hycoe, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Poma, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Peder Maller, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Persil, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Sun Maid raisins and prunes, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Ude og Hjemme, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Westerby, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Alfa margarine, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Beech-Nut chewing gum, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Roda Bjorn, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Ceraa, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Granulerat Chilisaltpeter, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Cutex, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Diamant, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Eastman Kodak, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Flint & Vaegen, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Fructus, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Goetjes Suebakker, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Gillette, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Gluten flour, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Flexo watch crystals, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Henkil & Co., undated (Film-reel 41)
  - Johannesburg (South Africa), undated; 10
    - General Motors, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet trucks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet passenger cars, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Marquette, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Oakland, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Oldsmobile, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Opel, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Pontiac, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Vauxhall, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Royal baking powder, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Murray & Stewart, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Moir's jellies, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Menek, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Karanan, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Jantzen, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Horlicks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Goodrich, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Electrolux, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Cream of Wheat, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Clubman shoes, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Black & White scotch, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Chateau brandy, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Atlantic Refineries, undated (Film-reel 41)
  - London (England, Great Britain), undated; 11
    - Pineoleum, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Odo-ro-no, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Marconiphone Loudspeaker, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - McVitie & Price Ltd., undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Lux soap and flakes, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Horlicks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Libby, McNeill & Libby, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Johnson Sea Horses, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Jantzen, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Ideal Hrue Dairies, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Royal baking powder, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Sun Maid raisins, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Swift's, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Vaseline, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Eastman Kodak (Cuba), undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Goodrich, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Hall's wines, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Harpic, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Pond's, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Pyrex, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Ramntree's candies, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Rinso, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Vauxhall, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Buick, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet trucks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet passenger cars, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Cadillac, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--LaSalle, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Marquette, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Atkinson face powder, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Beech-Nut chewing gum, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Bink's paint spray, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Boot's chemists, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Frank's Foods, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Brisling, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Chileau Nitrate Producers Association, Ltd., undated (Film-reel 41)
    - L.C. Smith and Corona, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Cream of Wheat, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Cutex, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Courtauldo rayon, undated (Film-reel 41)
  - Madrid (Spain), undated; 12
    - Hind's, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Horlicks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Jantzen, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Odo-ro-no, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Quaker Oats, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Vicente Rico, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Victor, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Royal baking powder, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Simmon's, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Coca-Cola, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Delco-Luy, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Eastman Kodak, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Frigidaire, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Gillette, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Goodrich, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet trucks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet passenger cars, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Oakland, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Opel, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--GMC, undated (Film-reel 41)
  - Paris (France), undated; 13
    - General Motors, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Buick, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet trucks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet passenger cars, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--GMC, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Marquette, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Oakland, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Oldsmobile, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Pontiac, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Coca-Cola, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Postal Telegraph, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Eastman Kodak, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Gillette, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Goodrich, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Victor, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Jantzen, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Johnson Sea Horses, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Libby, McNeill & Libby, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Quaker Oats, undated (Film-reel 41)
  - Sao Paulo (Brazil), undated; 14
    - Atlantic Refineries, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Blue Star Lines, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Casa Pratt, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Eastman Kodak, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Fleischmann's yeast for health, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Goodrich, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet trucks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet passenger cars, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Oakland, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Jantzen, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Johnson Sea Horses, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Maiyena, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Duryea, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Leite Moca, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - RCA tubes, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Refinacoes de Milbo Brasil, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Royal baking powder, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Casa Forte de Sul America, undated (Film-reel 41)
  - Stockholm (Sweden), undated; 15
    - Combri, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Cutex, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - DuPont Duco, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Ditzinger's, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Victor, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Layarin, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Lyon's tea, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Medital, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Modehurst, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Ovaltine, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Opel, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--GMC, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Buick, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet trucks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet passenger cars, undated (Film-reel 41)
  - Sydney (Australia), undated; 16
    - Pond's, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Potter & Moore, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Spaulding, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Nujol, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Flit, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Mistol, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Daggett & Rounsdell, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - J. Walter Thompson, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Matson Lines, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Lux soap and flakes, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Kraft, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Johnson Sea Horses, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Jantzen, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Horlicks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Chamberlain's cough medicine, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Australian Bedeaux, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Vauxhall, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Pontiac, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Oldsmobile, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Oakland, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet trucks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet passenger cars, undated (Film-reel 41)
  - Warsaw (Poland), undated; 17
    - Drazetki Bengalskie, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Saletra Chilyska, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Victor, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Gillette, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Pontiac, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Oldsmobile, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--LaSalle, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet trucks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet passenger cars, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Cadillac, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Buick, undated (Film-reel 41)
  - Wellington (New Zealand), undated; 18
    - Matson Lines, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Johnson Sea Horses, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - Horlicks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - CeCe radio tubes, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Bedford trucks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Vauxhall, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Pontiac, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet trucks, undated (Film-reel 41)
    - General Motors--Chevrolet passenger cars, undated (Film-reel 41)
- Western Office Accounts, 1916-1928; undated; 3
  - Kraft-Phenix, undated (Film-reel 42)
  - Libby, McNeill & Libby, 1916-1919 (Film-reel 42)
  - Libby, McNeill & Libby, 1919-1928 (Film-reel 43)
  - Swift & Co., undated (Film-reel 43)
  - Swift & Co., undated (Film-reel 44)
  - Swift & Co., undated (Film-reel 45)
- Copyright material stamped and returned from Washington, undated; 4
  - General Cigar, undated (Film-reel 45)
  - Pond's, undated (Film-reel 45)
  - Standard Brands, undated (Film-reel 45)
  - Chase & Sanborn, undated (Film-reel 45)
  - Tenderleaf Tea, undated (Film-reel 45)
  - Royal baking powder, undated (Film-reel 45)
  - Royal gelatine, undated (Film-reel 45)
  - Royal pudding, undated (Film-reel 45)
  - Fleischmann's Yeast for Health, undated (Film-reel 45)
  - Fleischmann's Irradiated Yeast for Animals, undated (Film-reel 45)
- Copy Approvals (Supplement to 16mm reel 40), 1936-1940; undated; 5
  - Lever Brothers (Lux Toilet Soap), undated (Film-reel 46)
    Dr. Killian, Breed, Abbott & Morgan (advertisements, coupons, leaflets), Dr. Susan scripts, Lux Radio Theatre commercials
  - General Cigar, undated (Film-reel 46)
    Special News Events consents, Vintage advertising consents
  - Pond's, undated (Film-reel 46)
    Client, Miss Olzendam, Dr. Killian, Dr. Andrews, Dr. Cipallaro, Mr. Clark and Mr. Voorhees (clients' lawyers)--radio comercials
  - Standard Brands, undated (Film-reel 46)
  - Chase & Sanborn, undated (Film-reel 46)
    Breed, Abbott & Morgan, Dr. Lee, Dr. Killian, Miss Olzendam/client
  - Tenderleaf Tea, undated (Film-reel 46)
    Dr. Lee, Dr. Killian, Miss Olzendam, client
  - Emerson Drug Co. (Bromo-Seltzer), undated (Film-reel 46)
  - Lever Brothers (Lux Toilet Soap), 1936-1940 (Film-reel 47)
    Dr. John Killian--newspapers 1937, magazines 1936-1940
  - General Cigar--White Owl, 1933-1936 (Film-reel 47)